budgetgolf.com 2017-07-08

# Home :: BudgetGolf Privacy Policy

BudgetGolf  II Inc. ("BudgetGolf") is committed to protecting online user privacy because we care. In order to ensure your privacy, information BudgetGolf collects through the BudgetGolf.com web site at www. BudgetGolf.com ("Site") is used only in the manner and for the purposes described in this BudgetGolf.com Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy.")

**User Consent to Privacy Policy**  
Any person accessing, browsing, or otherwise using the Site, either manually or via an automated device or program, shall be considered a "User." All Users are bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. Users consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable User information ("Information") pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collected from Users**  
BudgetGolf collects the email address of Users that email a question or comment to BudgetGolf or submit a customer review.

BudgetGolf collects the billing and shipping addresses, including relevant e-mail, phone and credit card numbers and expiration dates of Users who purchase a product from BudgetGolf through the Site. This includes Users who register to become BudgetGolf members, or those Users who enter any BudgetGolf contests or other promotional features available on the Site.

Through the use of "cookies" (For more information regarding Cookies, see below), BudgetGolf may collect and store anonymous information relating to Users' browsing patterns, including, for instance, the User's browser version, site referral information, IP address, operating system, and other technical Site use information.

**Cookies**  
The Site uses a feature of Internet Web browsers called a Cookie, which is a file that a User's Web browser places on a User's computer's hard drive, to assign an identification code to the computer and to collect anonymous browsing information. On this Site, cookies are used in conjunction with session variables to track a User's shopping cart and expire as soon as an order is completed or if a shopping cart sits idle for a lengthy period without being checked-out.

BudgetGolf does not use Cookies to retrieve Information about Users from a User's computer unless the User knowingly and willingly provided such Information. For instance, BudgetGolf’s cookies do not collect any Information and the cookies do not collect, store or contain any credit card information.

You may set your Internet Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent. If you prevent a cookie from being sent, you may limit the functionality BudgetGolf can provide you when you visit the Site, especially when purchasing an item on the Site.

**Use of Information**  
BudgetGolf uses the Information collected from its Users to:  
Respond to Users' questions or comments;  
Administer a User's contest entry or entry in other promotional feature;  
Fulfill a User's purchase request and notify Users of their order status;  
Provide Users with important functionality changes to the Site, new BudgetGolf.com services and special offers from BudgetGolf and reputable third parties that we think you will find valuable; and Mail a BudgetGolf or third party catalog to you.

**Updating or Deleting User Information**  
BudgetGolf offers Users who have provided Information to BudgetGolf an opportunity to review the Information provided to update or correct any errors. Users also can delete any Information provided to BudgetGolf or make choices about whether to receive special offers from BudgetGolf or any of our friends. To update or delete Information previously provided or to have your name removed from any mailing lists or other promotional distribution lists, email us at [sales@BudgetGolf.com](mailto:sales@BudgetGolf.com) and we will take care of your request for you.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
BudgetGolf may disclose information about our Users to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of BudgetGolf or others. BudgetGolf may disclose Information to a third party in the event that another company acquires BudgetGolf or part of its assets.

**Option to Limit Sharing with Third Parties**  
BudgetGolf understands that Users do not want spam or junk mail. We only share your Information with reputable companies who provide products or services that we believe interest our customers. Because we care, all Users always can choose whether or not their Information is shared with other companies, and all Users can change their minds at any time. In order to make a choice, do the following: send an e-mail to [sales@BudgetGolf.com ](mailto:sales@BudgetGolf.com)or call BudgetGolf at 815-630-2098

**Linked Internet Web Sites**  
The Site may provide hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or may take you to a third party website not controlled by BudgetGolf. These hyperlinked third party websites may collect and disclose Information different than this Site. BudgetGolf is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these web sites, and BudgetGolf expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

**Children**  
The [BudgetGolf.com](http://www.budgetgolf.com/) Site is not directed towards children under 13 years of age and BudgetGolf does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age through the Site.

**Security**  
Because we care, this Site has security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information under our control, including credit card information that is submitted to BudgetGolf. When Users place orders or access their account information, the Site uses secure server software (SSL), which encrypts all information Users' input before it is sent to us. In addition, we do not store User's credit card numbers in their online accounts so if someone obtains your account log in information, they will not be able to view a User's credit card number. Thus, we have taken steps to protect the Information we collect from you from unauthorized access. Unfortunately, no system is perfect; therefore, BudgetGolf makes no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. BudgetGolf shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Privacy Policy because of a security breach or technical malfunction.

**Sale or** **Acquisition**  
In the event that another company acquires BudgetGolf or all or part of its assets, we reserve the right to include Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

**Applicable Law/International Issues**  
Information that is submitted to this Site will be collected, processed, stored, disclosed and disposed of in accordance with applicable U.S. law. If you are a non-U.S. User, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your Information, as discussed above, outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, such Information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. U.S. law may not provide the degree of protection for Information that is available in other countries. By providing us with your Information, you acknowledge that your have read this Privacy Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such Information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site, but if you have already provided us with Information, please contact us at [sales@BudgetGolf.com](mailto:sales@BudgetGolf.com) and let us know how you would like us to handle such information.

**Amendments to Privacy Policy**  
BudgetGolf reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy periodically. Any amendments made to this Privacy Policy will be considered effective ten (10) days after the amendments are posted on the Site. You should check the Site periodically to review the most recent Privacy Policy.

**Contact Information**  
If Users have any questions about our services or Privacy Policy, please contact:

BudgetGolf Customer Service  
3307 Corporate Drive  
Joliet, IL  60431  

815-630-2098

Amended: January 12th, 2017
